and we are back welcome home everyone it's been a minute yeah it has been two weeks yeah two weeks
two weeks 10 days off um and yeah i'm i'm excited like uh it's good to be back
yes yeah so how was your little break it was good yeah i had a break my mac mimi didn't yeah
that's the goal right like the new slaves or computers now yes exactly so it was good to be
on holiday and that was good to actually be forced to use uh your mic mini from a large distance and
to keep on going creating new branches new new commits and everything yes now exactly like uh
that was a nice experience that you you're doing literally nothing but still the the pull requests
are coming out yes you're just checking your your phone for notifications yeah oh bro like uh i went
so i went away in the in the it was by night yes and uh around like two three m i checked and i had
the github authorization issues i said fuck i can't validate with my computer because like uh
codex was telling me yeah uh you need to click on your computers and stuff oh i'm not on my computer
so um can you give me a mobile link to click it to it's a yeah i can do that okay yeah it does
everything exactly i had fable connected so to my uh to my app on my phone nice and i gave it full
access to my mac mini because it's it only has the code on it nothing else only some projects
and it doesn't matter what i asked it it just said i can do that for you no problem yeah it
reminds you like the uh uh open cloud day yeah only better much better uh it works this works
and even if it doesn't work you ask it to get a workaround or to give a solution and says oh we
can do this this and this yeah perfect oh yeah no it's not like it's it's a new year and um
it's even like getting better with the all of the new models that we got during those 10 days
yes yeah and also what you do is like talking to cloud on mobile right cloud on mobile or codex
yeah yeah cloud on mobile yeah yeah i do and it doesn't matter just one of the two that's good
enough i i use codex because uh we get more results so uh i burn three resets during those
10 days though that's a lot how many projects were you handling so i had automation for 10 projects
like non-critical projects like small stuff um like a couple of mobile apps like a tv show tracker
for me and my girlfriend so we can share the show then the share the status of the show so that's
cool um the meta bar like the codex bar but uh mine and it's better than peter codex bar it's
better um what do they do a couple of other projects and uh yeah uh website factory for
restaurants because that's gonna be the first autonomous company that fully autonomous company
that i want to lunch and uh jen feed what did i what else did i do okay i can check
and uh yeah some other non-critical project uh the game stuff i continue also those like much slower
like not every two or three hours uh just less like four hours for those ones just because you can
yeah exactly i also know i use figma so i had a routine to uh put all of the screen to figma
because the mcp and also the mcp is uh limited to 200 calls a day so uh i had a daily routine
to just burn those 200 maximize it yeah uh max sweep like the cleaner like the tools to clean
your hard drive on your mac after all of those walkthroughs and branches uh open tv tracker
that's done uh ship code yeah ship code too and uh yeah in the games that's it yeah around 10
10 custom uh thing customers 10 project like that love it and you just burned every token available
like everything i've run two subscription on cloud and uh four weekly equivalent of codex on with me
awesome and it's everything is coming out uh so now it's getting honestly it's getting uh i
shipped it didn't like uh just burn token to burn token like the project are coming out now
like meta is done i'll send you the link sorry uh ship code uh i need to check it i need to qa
and the other same thing like qa or more progress so nice well i think if you do the intro
we see the numbers oh [ __ ] that's even better
so yeah okay i actually didn't think about that we can edit it after so that's no problem
um okay but we we're not doing videos anymore do we yeah maybe a small one i don't know it is better
to have shorts right yes yeah we don't know okay so um okay we went away for 10 days but codex and
claud didn't take any time off while we were on the beach swimming while we were on the beach um those
our agent uh keep shipping pull requests every hour and we are going to show you what we have
shipped and uh not not how much money we made because that's that's no first you have to build
yeah and we are going to show you which product we are shipped and how we are uh
how we set up those automation so subscribe like the video and uh enjoy
cool nice cool good job i need to check because i think
oh let me connect my mouse okay
so now i can scroll because i built in a cost tracker oh you too yeah yeah but i make a
difference between how much costs are made within my subscription that i just pay like the 90 for
cloud or the 200 or whatever and then i made a difference in what do i actually use in adi cost
and i have one cloud um 200 subscription connected and i have one codex 90 subscription connected
and in during my holiday i've burned for 3109 worth of tokens yeah i'm not surprised so that's
a 10x yeah yeah no like uh for for codex i think we we get like worth uh 15 grain of token and uh
for cloud we get 5k or something yeah that's possible because uh cloud was 2100 and codex
was almost 1k yeah and i'm using codex to do the review so that's less yeah okay nice and this is
just on the the uh on the task that i put in the system this is not everything i did additional on
the side myself only the automation part yeah okay but that that's big paying like 300 dollars and
getting 3k in 10 days back yeah i mean if you can convert that into dollars that's a win right
that's employees basically yeah yeah for sure yeah like the goal for us is like to convert those
tokens into dollars and that's all well it's just getting projects and just having oh having us
automate your business because we know how to automate yeah and uh i i i think like with those
all of those release i think we are getting like really close to uh the quality of the output is
good enough to be fully automated maybe it was like a human uh reviewing the like yeah remain
in the loop to review at the end but like it's getting there yeah i had codex 5.6 soul review
my opus and after five rounds of reviewing they would give me a final result if it went wrong
and sometimes they had like really good issues they found stuff that honestly i don't know if
i would have found it correctly but you don't know if those issues are real or not though like
you know like because sometimes it can find something that's not here yeah if you say it
has to do a cli check it has to do a discount notification it doesn't have the right to do it
then it will crash on it but that's why i have cloud fable connected on that mega mini who runs
everything it can fix it can give the the rights that are needed and everything you use m s or open
claw to orchestrate those subscription yeah nope everything was built by myself by fable yeah
yeah and i i don't feel i have the need for those it was like one day of work and i didn't even sit
at my pc i just told him what to do and it's on the side working and then i come back and i say
hey i'm missing this and it does it yeah no exactly because even like if you so i updated
my global and codex and claud when um opus 5 dropped so even like to change the aliases even
like to set up the orchestration to tell claud to use uh gpt 5.6 as a subagent or even like they
can talk to each other plus define the aliases so now if it's opus it will always be the latest opus
i know gpt something like i use like a 5.6 so i for everything yeah me too yeah um
and uh but like what's hammers doing more than that i don't know and honestly
i don't want external software built by someone else on my pc because i don't know what they're
putting in exactly yeah and again you are like one prompt away of like uh implementing yourself
and you have you know what's up right yeah so why should i do it if we can do it better ourselves
and easier now we have the tokens because we have big subscriptions i mean uh kind of like uh i
i burn my clothes subscription uh i think it's because of the skill and mcp like i burn them
in two days uh yeah that's that's going hard i got i got the reset on friday and on monday afternoon
so okay i'm gonna use codex now yeah but that's the cool thing here every time that i see that
i'm burning a lot the first question i ask is hey we are burning so fast this is impossible to
maintain what can we do to make it burn less tokens uh and if he needs to set up something
manual just do it but improve it and that works yeah all the time yeah and even like i saw some
tweets about like one of the french entrepreneurs saying like yeah on friday um i just clean up
my context or like my cloud md and like the agent.md because it gets so much shit so fast
uh even on twitter you can yeah i don't know if you saw that but um some people were saying uh
for opus 5 direct your skill and uh review your cloud and then the model will
work better oh that's cool yeah so you need like a big cleanup
uh yeah so did you use uh opus 5 uh i just started using it yeah but i did it only in
a terminal i didn't add it to my automation yet because i didn't want to crash everything by
accident when i was like uh 1600 kilometers away yeah you know what uh what you do like it's what
when it works don't break it right yeah yeah exactly and just make sure that you have full
access i did have access because unify has these uh travel routers it is amazing not promoting a
product but uh i have the entire unify setup at home okay and they have a travel router so
in the apartment that we rented i just put their uh router uh internet cable into my unify router
put this power in and it set up a local vp network with the same thing as at home and a vpn connection
to my home router my firewall oh that's slick so working in spain i was on my dutch ip all the time
working from my home lab for my home and all the ip filters everything was set up just within five
minutes that's sick that's pretty cool yeah okay because uh before i was changing my aws
cloud watch to access my instance from airbnb ip yeah yeah that's not fun i have ip blocks
everywhere yeah so i just have to travel router i put it in and i get my own wi-fi all the devices
are instantly connected and i'm using my home ip address that's nice interesting how much does it
cost the thing costs like 70 or 80 euros but you have to set up your entire unify network at home
as well and that's a bit more expensive um but again it works perfectly can't you connect it to
delscall to be part of the network yeah you can but i like this because it just works yeah and
it's tech so it's cool to have um that that's interesting um okay what about the 5.6 soul like
what's your feedback on it sometimes it's annoying or is it just me yeah like yeah this morning i was
mad against it cloud fable just worked perfectly like like a good employee and then 5.6 it just
does weird stuff and then when you say why are you doing this it didn't give you the task to do it
and you are now changing a lot of stuff that was working and said oh yeah you're right it's like
going back in time yeah we're just arguing with the ai all the time this one goes rogue more like
it um i had the issue with like version like the deployer versioning and it was just instead of
increasing the patch she was uh increasing the minor so every deployment had a new minor fucking
release yeah like stuff like that and and oh yeah this morning so uh i had you know like the so i
have um the authorization as a custom like uh just don't ask me the just just go don't ask me for
github authorization so like yes to everything yes and this fucker wrote the whole branch into
uh the temp folder and the temp folder doesn't have the authorization of um the authorization
like the perms yeah so it was asking me to use github come online like github pull request
create the github read github read it was asking me to confirm a github read i said bro stop doing
that and uh 30 minutes after then i found the you know in the block of files edited it was all in
prior in temp temp folder say why the fuck did you do that yeah and i think this is one of the
perfect examples why you need us just yeah because we understand what what goes wrong yeah i don't
know exactly other people just have to delete everything and restart and hope that it doesn't
make the same mistake and eventually after two days of testing they get it working
um we just know why it's not working yeah no exactly i mean you're not never like
uh you never know if you are you are going to find the bug solution in the next five minutes
or five hours right yeah but knowing what you're doing and then debugging and asking the right
questions that helps a lot oh but uh i mean
those instruction file like the cloud and the agent.md we are like the models are still not
listening to it nope nuts no but that's why i like review rounds because eventually i force uh in a
first review round to check everything versus the agents.md and the readme.md files oh so even when
opus does the first coding even if it skips some parts then i have a rule in the first uh checking
round from codex that it checks the readme the agents and everything and it compares it to what
has been coded and that has been going good so far because i log um the conversation between the two
agents i just tell them to write down all the findings and then opus has to reply on each finding
and why he thinks it's correct why he thinks it's not correct so i can read back the entire
conversation they had and it's really funny to see they even say you are wrong but like
all of that shit goes to the context window no i just write it in comments under the issue
in github oh yeah in the thread right but like the whole conversation between codex
and cloud is it not going into the context of your session yeah it is but it's max yeah
but it's max five five rounds and then i just clear everything okay so it's per task yeah
okay okay that makes sense yeah okay so you have a thread on on github or in the md file uh yeah
well they do it in md file but eventually they write it in a comment on github in the issue so
that i can see the issue what was written down and see the entire conversation yeah that makes sense
i love i love github look for tracking like the agent stuff yeah i just hope they keep it as a
good software because it had some issues lately last week he had like a uh 500 there or like i
was not able to use github for i think half a day or a couple of implementation like yeah i can't
read that's a big issue bro like github goes down there is no more software in the world yeah and
the weird thing is almost everybody uses it and when you speak to somebody using gitlab or
something they say yeah we use gitlab but it doesn't have all the options get a pass
yeah no way yeah yeah it's yeah i know it's uh but like i also wants to build its own
agentic competition to github yeah so elon is building it well yeah we'll see how it goes
but uh okay so we talk about 4.65 febble five febble bro febble five oh uh it's going away in
seven days yeah going away we're gonna keep it for another seven days
no my joke is falling because they keep saying that it was going away again and again three times
but we knew it yeah as soon as they have competition they won't if they delete it from
subscription they will lose people and they use they lose subscribers no for sure but still like
cloud looks better than 5.6 right like yeah for for all the front end tasks as soon as i
i start talking to codex uh i'm getting i'm getting anxiety because i know the front will be
shit but i also don't get it it's like they have been telling us so many times fable went out
and you only still only get 50 percent of your subscription in fable tokens yes and now they
released opus 5 and on some parts fable is better but i'm coding opus is better and you can just use
it at half the price 100 of your subscription so what's the use of fable maybe some cyber stuff
that's all of this basic uh yeah all of the stuff we don't do but for coding like crud apps it's
fine yeah but even if you use fable to do it after you you did coding you just do it for a check
and you can just have fable check everything and you're still within your limit easily oh
yeah like i'm not i'm not implementing anything with fable fable is too precious like it's only
doing the the planning right yeah and uh yeah and the execution on 5.6 that's all right okay so i
can say save my cloud subscription but also like we are we have a bonus right now on the session
right so we are like 50 percent more so we need to like until the august of the end of the week
we have rotation but after that limitation or going down what's going on with like the the
the deal with ellen are they not you're supposed to have like more compute now
yeah i damn it doesn't it they have a different uh a different promotion every time yeah
oh what what every time they have a different promotion so now they are saying you have it
until august but before they had it as well i just keep keep getting free resets i don't know
but i always get enough tokens so i don't mind and uh reset on codex like uh on entropic side
i'm waiting for them like they need the button they need a better yeah yeah but they will they
have to compete so they will add something eventually yeah the only thing i still haven't
tried was the new grok oh yes uh now we have it in europe like it has been available um
uh last week i think so we had the two two weeks delay on grok um yeah i i have it i need to run
it it's it's included in the meta bar uh monitoring so i have a backup ai stuff but i don't know yeah
we need to test it but um yeah but if it can do a a final check or whatever even if you use it
for simple things maybe it finds more than codex does or something different that will be awesome
what was the benchmark on 4.5 it was good yeah benchmark 4.5 grass is
oh 4.5 grok because i'm gonna get opus uh tech man's studio
tank path
uh okay what the fuck is benchmark i don't think i'm gonna use that
oh yeah uh grok is way cheaper though than uh 4.8 at the time uh artificial artificial analysis yes
intelligence so opus five faber five yeah that was fun oh it's just outside of the window yes
perfect claud is one point above faber five opus five max
yeah so it's almost the same quality kimi three yeah okay open source model that's gonna be fun
too yeah but did you see how much ram you needed for the kimi tree oh yeah you know but you need
open source model doesn't need it's gonna run on your computer right it just need it means it's it
it means it's coming from china yeah it is but i i think they block new subscribers really you're
not getting it yeah because eventually uh when cloud was up almost at full usage and they wanted
to keep selling subscription they just halved all the capacity from everybody and kimi said okay we
are almost at full capacity we block all new people coming in so if you have a subscription
you're lucky and otherwise you're out of luck you can't get one so i don't know if they opened it by
now but this shows a big difference in how they treat it damn oh yeah kimi just ended premium ai
subscription what the fuck that was okay wait that was one week ago yeah it was one i don't know if
they upgraded the usage at this moment uh has received far more love than we expected and our
gps are feeling it over the past 48 hours the moon has pushed close to the limit of occurring
capacity to protect the experience of existing subscribers we are temporarily posing new
subscription and practice compute for current members wow jesus uh gimme ai yeah i think this
is good they just give give you what you pay for that's perfect okay uh where's the okay again
don't even have fucking uh kimi pricing
no there is no pricing what the heck yeah let me check
i think you have to sign up first yeah and i didn't sign up yet but this shows that if you
want to have an open model that's going good you better get a subscription yeah and then just pay
for it because once you're out you're out and i even don't know if it's possible to upgrade
oh this is it why am i in italian
allegrito i like what wait is that is that the what the whole the name they are playing
yeah because you have english below it what wait what yeah yeah this is good
okay and you can just say join waitlist
where oh fuck you have scroll like five times over it yeah it's a white button damn really
damn well yeah i was talked on the fucking allegro stuff yeah why are you doing setting music stuff
because it's possible okay yeah why not uh so even on the annually plan you have to join a waitlist
yes okay fair enough new membership plan coming yeah we really need more compute
yeah yeah yeah we if you want to keep scaling we do that's crazy i mean yeah so that that
means like even the inference battle like uh elon musk is right then because uh that's that's the
game in town because nobody can offer the best model to the people at full capacity like no but
for the easy things you can do it locally i'm using olama on a 16 gigabyte ram just for chatting
communicating and giving me answers on the open progress and everything yeah really you can only
say hello and then maybe it works okay it's like i have fable connected to my mcmini but also i have
olama it's connected to discord and if i want to know how many tasks are open what the status of
a task is and everything but olama also builds a database of every task that i've put in so
it has uh like a database in the back end and i can just say hey okay um give me an overview
of what we did for this customer on this task okay it'll give me all the tasks which which model do
you run on olama um i don't know fable chose it oh maybe you have mistral you are one of the user of
mistral and you don't know it i then i don't know it but it works really good and then it is on the
same mcmini yeah it's like a local vector database that's it yeah okay it's like the equivalent of
your eco uh model basically yeah and that's good enough and for those small questions just getting
status updates i save all those tokens yeah oh now warps onto like yeah i mean uh yeah if i if i
use all of my cloud i can always have olama or slash croc uh alternative stuff um but okay no
yeah we were talking about grok and on the benchmark yeah it's uh so kimi three kimi yeah
kimi three and just after yeah after yeah i would just say even if you don't want it just join the
wait list because you never know when they are scaling up and if they do it by the time that
they make an even better model then you wish you had joined it in time that's nuts that's nuts uh
new oh yeah like nvidia is starting to do some uh models too well you have to start somewhere
yeah uh tuck and muse yeah also like the same day uh mark uh the camera like dropped the
facebook model did you try it nope yeah me neither do people even want to try a facebook model
because facebook is known for selling all your data yeah like so why give them even more on ai
exactly all right and again like entropic and codex are in my workflow now so i don't have a
point i'm not even using grok and i have installed it and i don't even talk to it so well i think
that's the thing right once the setup in your entire infrastructure and you're making money so
you don't care that it costs like a few hundred dollars then they are not leaving unless they have
a big fallback and other models are much better yeah i mean maybe there is a play for open source
model i don't know but okay so yeah about the cost per task that's nuts yeah that's crazy
uh why is that so expensive like it's twice 5.6 to run cloud opus max
than 5.6 max like what yeah but this is just the ai tokens compared
yeah true and you get like a bigger multiplier in your subscription so eventually for you it's
cheaper yeah and also like the cost wait our weighted average cost usd pair intelligence
tasks so laura is better yeah thank you um no that's the cost of the time so it's not the token
used anyway it's just like how much it costs to do one task right oh so it's all relative it's not
the cost per token yeah i thought it was for the token usage for the same task and then comparing
it on different models yeah but wait that doesn't make sense because like deep seek why not everyone
is using deep seek if we have a task and cost two bucks with opus everyone should use deep seek yeah
but don't you think that for sure companies in the us here the deep seek is from china and they just
don't trust it that there is a huge discussion right now on twitter about that because um
right did you have you seen like the attack from uh the next model from open ai that hacked again
face yeah and then you again faced uh again face use a chinese model like open source because they
were not able to use fable or 5.6 because it was uh too much of a quad rail stuff oh i missed that
one i just i only read that open ai had a model going rogue and hacking logging face yes and they
didn't even notice it in the first few days yes and i didn't check anything further and the the
rest of the story the last uh 20 of the story i missed it i tried to use fable and then there's
fable told them oh you know it's a security uh go back to 4.8 and then 4.8 was not able to uh
attack them that would defend them properly so they installed kimi uh three or two maybe whatever
one of the kimi instance and then they were able to defend themselves again the attack
oh that's cool they use a chinese model to defend themselves against a u.s model yeah that was
supposed to help them yeah that seems fun yeah i think they should just tell open ai we want
a full year of free tokens for this shit yeah exactly i mean yeah click one two uh three more
times reset button please yeah but eventually this shows that you need some good devs to understand
how to use models and everything and to defend your company because it's gonna be fun yeah
this is going wild do you still have a clear vision of the architecture of all of the projects
that you've encoded in the next in the last 12 months um yes and no yeah would you be able to
stop using ai and keep working yes well except for two projects because i did two test projects
uh where i had them build a website with sas product and i said everything needs to be ai
built i don't want to do anything um and every time that i have tokens left in my account yeah
i just burn them on those projects but they are not like my main focus but on everything
i do for a customer i still do all the writing down of the the projects at least i discuss them
with the ai i read everything and i know how the infrastructure works all right okay yeah
more sense yeah like uh you your customers are doing like half a million a day so
yeah they need to be secure yeah and uh where when do you think you will stop looking at the card
uh i don't think i will do it in the next two years yeah of course you keep trusting your ai
more and more and more because it finds so much stuff that to be honest some some projects that
we have been working on for for years and have been working perfectly it found an issue like
created five years ago and it never went wrong it never had something but um i've been sharing
it in some groups and other people had the same issue as well so but it's like the defining the
leak that has been in linux for 16 years yeah no exactly it's the same thing yeah it's they
will always find something so you trust on it to fix it but you still want to know what it does
the problem is like when you catch the ai doing something wrong it will it's really really wrong
and uh so then it it makes me like question everything that uh you have done and just
like pushed uh just like that yeah and uh you don't know what the fuck it introduced
yeah and then the question is what other ai can you ask to check the entire project
yeah and and there is like some um articles on x that uh turn about like talk about like
yeah the software factory uh don't really doesn't really work right now because uh again like it's
spaghetti code and stuff and when you have a bug in production at 3m uh you have no idea how to
debug it uh without a cloud subscription or something like that so maybe at scale that's
gonna be a problem yeah yeah yeah and then bigger companies for sure yeah but uh and also okay yeah
also like um i saw uh levels uh io saying that the revenue of the is in the acer um project are
all going down because of ai because of ai and because like the value um the value of his
software is not high enough to uh um to not be vibe coded and also his audience are like tech
bros so they will vibe code everything yeah like he is giving them free information on how to do it
exactly but plus like everyone is also uh a tech guys on on x right like his audiences are techies
so that everyone has a club subscription yeah um uh could i talk about the good and bad one
i notice our signup conversion are pretty weak this month uh everything is downstream of us
getting less traffic to the site also like yeah like people are not going to the website anymore
they just like uh speak with uh creativity uh i find myself using cloud less and less yeah true
what's the answer no short fix next to explore other channel youtube newsletter etc um and levels
um i'm seeing a trend here declining reunion traffic with indie hackers on my own project too
maybe big bc project too but i will not know because they don't share revenue
to me it's unclear like big ai is cannibalizing everything that used to be apps not by by the way
just time to changing into that um yeah that's that's a big drop but that's uh the guy from uh
tailwind nobody is going to the website because now the agent knows how to use the framework
yeah so it doesn't have visit at all uh made you for tailwind nobody needs to read the
documentation anymore exactly no no exactly like you just check visually what's the components
you want in your code base and then you just drop it right um tech take a close but you got some
other counter examples okay correlation project just gonna keep going these guys tweeting a lot
yeah but does he also tweet about the functionality in his project
not really but i think like look like his bio yeah yeah he used his bio as a fucking uh
yeah driver because honestly if i can just have uh cloud scrape his entire uh x account also the
products and the mentions of the products i can just make a full documentation of everything he
asks how he's doing it what he's coding about it what he's telling about it that makes it so easy
to just copy his products yeah exactly i mean it like we are in the industrialization phase of
apps right but um so okay uh your application is the report okay so this is a common reply but i
need to see my girlfriend yeah i uh i see my girlfriend who also stopped using most sass and
just ask claud and chat gpt whatever she wants and now evan makes her own apps to solve program
uh highly personalized and a firmware interface we predicted air will generate on the fly to solve
whatever problem now we have it's happening and it's here yeah and it's the same thing right
people are looking for mcp's to connect everything but you don't need an mcp you can just give cloud
your apis exactly just can build everything you want and you don't even know it's mcp you just
ask claud to figure it out yeah uh so that was the uh answer like uh is your application is developer
india facing you might have a hard time competing with self-made solution if your customers are
consumer and smbs most people don't like seeing uh tinkering or making their own solution yeah well
now you will see who are the people out of their creative they will just go with flow and use the
new and latest ais to keep on building something that is used and not keep doing the indie stuff
yeah and it's a new era man like uh internet is changing for real uh
there is a tweet fuck i should have maybe i did book market back uh nope
nope nope i didn't fuck
okay too bad but um yeah that was like one guy saying uh we are still serving
um our customers are smbs and they don't have like the like for example um
uh yeah hairstyle salon or stylist or nail lady will not build her own cloud website app stuff
yeah i think people will because i i have some marketing agencies who are now
instead of hiring uh designers just using cloud.ai design yeah but they're already marketing uh
companies yeah but they have no knowledge of design or whatever and it does everything for them
yeah but i'm talking about like the nail lady that uh doing nails ah yeah even if she just
asked cloud and asked them people are building their own websites how do i do it and cloud says
hey here tell me what you want go to design and you will get a website and they can even
just ask them how to deploy it yeah that will be automated and imagine cloud selling aws hosting
that will be an insane product with big margins there is sites now on chat gpt that you can host
uh a website on chat gpt directly yeah that can kill the entire hosting industry
but like bro you say the multiply like a nails lady doesn't ever use that tool you know it it's
but if she asks how do i visit it and how do my my customers see the website then cloud knows
she means deploy yeah yeah yeah how do i get my customers seeing this website yeah yeah that's
enough yeah and then says oh hey it needs to be online normally you need a hosting party but
please click here pay me ten bucks it will be live yeah give me the api key stuff there whatever yeah
um okay maybe last section i think we uh what about um okay no just just back on the last part
didn't uh cloud because i'm not using the cloud desktop app didn't have the browser included yes
then it's fixed it will go to a hosting website for you until you pay here yeah and it will just
log in get the ftp in your account or the api or whatever and it will connect it will upload and
that's it there is even the ios simulator now inside the app so how cool would it be if we just
automate a hosting party and the only thing we do is try to get into uh chat gpt and tell
chat gpt that if it has a customer pay here we will just show instantly and share the ftp so
the chat gpt sells customers to us then we need to be good at the geo so yeah the high reference
stuff so then we need gen feed to spam ugc videos about oh yeah most thing yeah solved yeah next
product is incoming okay let's go i mean feel um you know like the the content creator guy he
built his own uh um i don't know infrastructure but like hosting leg bed product stuff i don't
exactly why i did that but uh because it doesn't have servers so behind it is that like what uh
amazon i think so but still so many people on expose they built something and eventually it
was a prompt to cloud and they don't know how it works but it works and they say hey look what i've
built look look matt look look what matt schumer built uh one prompt uh cloud five opus five yeah
that's insane and he also gave the prompt right yes you get you get the yeah yes yeah so uh first
person shooter building a brother with 3gs and web gl2 there is no art assets
uh texture bla bla bla tuning performances before optimization after yeah okay
honest assessment the goal was too much a modern commodity it does not yeah no shit
uh okay felt short uh hands block blocks blocky fingers material machine surfaces read as
procedural noise characters enemy reads as manicure at distance indirect light blah blah blah
but all of that you can you can fix it with like some um 3d generation from codex or cloud or
whatever yeah this was a one shot and then it's optimizing yeah uh where is the two where is the
prompt prompt i want you to build a first person shooter that's three lines yeah working nuts but
then eventually cloud uh decided everything by himself yeah so does everybody who puts in this
this prompt get the same result uh yeah i saw some people uh having similar output
uh zero shot uh gpt yeah awesome uh i'm pretty sure it's match rumor
uh okay okay
where is it fuck yes uh my tumor was right i don't game it so i'm almost a boomer and i
already learned to cut three years ago with ai my son was there one prompt shared my view on ai
gaming completely my son has been a gamer his entire life he was everything i kept asking
whatever what do you buy when i saw much from a post one prompt a 20-hour run on ultra jesus
fucking christ that's expensive at the end of it my son had a playable build specifically for him
running on a 85 inch tv yep yeah and then seeing like gaming studios working for years on it
it's lego style yeah lego that's that's cool
downtown yeah
bro that's that's sick a 20 number 20 yeah a 20 yeah fair question i asked us to pull the receive
the run is 24 million token across 85 sub agent and 8 000 tool calls
oh wait
he put it online yeah he published it yes it deployed exactly
like the question have other people play my game yeah oh wait wait okay i'm gonna i'm gonna
close it because it killed my computer it's probably it's heavy it downloads everything and
yeah maybe i should not click some links on x there is still a difference between building a
shooter game that one person plays and building a shooter game that like 50 million people at
the same time i know exactly like it's like oh yeah i want to rebuild the twitch for live
streaming yeah you have no idea how video network works right so enjoy but yeah looks like my own
version is loading on through 3gs bro it looks good yeah like it's just one shot like remember
what we produce with one shot stuff like the in the arena like that's that's 10 times better
than the fucking arena we had it was only a few weeks ago yeah i'm still like mental uh yeah also
this i know that's not the game i sent you but like the space stuff cloth punk jesus
whoa yeah also the entire gaming industry is changing not just development and coding
clairvoyance to make quality using matrimor prompt second shot 120 at 4k what the heck
that's mental
and probably it has cloud scraping all this data of people discussing what they want better
and they just load it in for the next next version oh yeah yeah because yeah then i'm
sure because the data and yeah and everybody is publishing live what they like and what they
don't like so the only thing they need is scrape it load it in improve it and push it to the next
office version and people will be blown away oh it's so much better this time well yeah you told
her what should be better yeah exactly plus like yeah everyone like can push it like open source
on github blah blah you get the code and you can get the git history see yeah you can even avoid
like the git history and have the best output at the end like yeah it's not like the wall is wide
man like it's getting even better yes every 10 days at the time so what are you going to do next
i'm trying to finish the project the 25 project i'm working on right now yeah uh because yeah like
we can we can start a new prompt and like one from something but at the end of the day you
need to transform those tokens into money right yes so yeah but again after this like 10 days
experience stuff like those um autonomous company like if it's think as an it's it's like sold out
and playing out as an autonomous company i think there is like shit ton of stuff that could be done
and even like with the speed of ai you if you don't talk to ai bros there is a world when
you can have a sustainable business at least for a few months slash years and uh it's enough
fully output ai stuff yeah because there is a new step with like those uh opus five favorite five
five point six so it's racial yeah yeah what do you think what's your take i think i would say
let's go yeah let's go just just keep the pace up keep going keep coding see what works drop the
other parts and don't try to do too much yourself because the next version will even be better
yeah i i that's true it's hard to do something that's gonna survive the next model too right
yeah yeah okay man i think we could wrap it up here yeah yes we can make some amazing shorts
yes that's i think that's the goal so yeah subscribe to the channel because maybe we're
not gonna do any more videos anymore it's gonna be shorter and it's gonna be live stream only
yes and let us know what you think yes thank you so much uh enjoy the rest of your weeks
Thank you, Mitchell. And see you in the chat. Yes.